export const multipleQuizBeginner = {
    totalQuestions: 15,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is the primary role of a "web developer"?',
        answers: ["Creating and managing a website's database", 'Developing front-end components of a website', 'Designing and developing websites', 'Compiling website content'],
        correctAnswer: 'Designing and developing websites',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What does "debugging" mean in web development?',
        answers: ["The process of creating a website's visual layout", 'The process of identifying and fixing errors in source code', "Efforts to improve a website's speed and efficiency", ' Scrolling a webpage up or down'],
        correctAnswer: 'The process of identifying and fixing errors in source code',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'How is "user experience (UX)" related to web development?',
        answers: ['Focuses on website security', 'Focuses on how users interact with a website and how easy it is for them to navigate', 'The process of delivering website content to users', "Efforts to improve a website's speed"],
        correctAnswer: 'Focuses on how users interact with a website and how easy it is for them to navigate',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What does "responsive design" mean in web development?',
        answers: [' Designing websites that are not responsive to user devices', 'Using large-sized images on a website', 'Creating links on a website', 'Designing website layouts to fit various screen sizes'],
        correctAnswer: 'Designing website layouts to fit various screen sizes',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What does "web hosting" mean in English?',
        answers: ['The process of optimizing images on a website', 'Scrolling a webpage up or down', 'A service that stores and provides access to a website over the internet', "Designing a website's visual layout"],
        correctAnswer: 'A service that stores and provides access to a website over the internet',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What does "API (Application Programming Interface)" mean in web development?',
        answers: ['A set of rules and protocols allowing various software components to interact', "The process of creating a website's visual layout", "The process of designing a website's user interface", "The process of delivering website content to users"],
        correctAnswer: 'A set of rules and protocols allowing various software components to interact',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'How is "cross-browser compatibility" related to web development?',
        answers: ['Focuses on grammar usage in website content', "Efforts to improve a website's speed", 'Ensuring that a website functions well across various web browsers', "Developing front-end components of a website"],
        correctAnswer: 'Ensuring that a website functions well across various web browsers',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What does "content management system (CMS)" mean in English?',
        answers: ['Scrolling a webpage up or down', 'A system for easily creating and editing website content', 'The process of identifying and fixing errors in source code', "A set of rules and protocols allowing software components to communicate"],
        correctAnswer: 'A system for easily creating and editing website content',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'How would you describe "server-side scripting" in web development?',
        answers: ['Executing source code on the client-side (browser)', 'The process of optimizing images on a website', "Designing a website's visual layout", "Executing source code on the server-side to generate webpages"],
        correctAnswer: 'Executing source code on the server-side to generate webpages',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What does "back-end development" mean in the context of web development?',
        answers: ["Developing a website's visual layout", 'Developing front-end components of a website', 'Developing the parts of a website not visible to users', "Designing a website's visual layout"],
        correctAnswer: 'Developing the parts of a website not visible to users',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: 'When you click a link on a webpage, you are taken to another page',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'The "browser address bar" is where you enter the address of a website you want to visit',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: '"User experience (UX)" focuses on website security',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: '"Debugging" is the process of creating a websites visual layout',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: ' "Web Performance Optimization" aims to improve a websites search engine ranking',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
    ],
  };



export const multipleQuizIntermediate = {
    totalQuestions: 15,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What does "SEO" stand for in web development?',
        answers: ["Search Engine Organization", 'Site Editing Operations', 'Search Engine Optimization', 'Site Efficiency Operations'],
        correctAnswer: 'Search Engine Optimization',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which of the following best describes "UI/UX design"?',
        answers: ["Designing the visual layout and user experience of a website", 'A process of debugging source code', "The process of optimizing images on a website", 'Creating content for a website'],
        correctAnswer: 'Designing the visual layout and user experience of a website',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is the purpose of "cookies" in web development?',
        answers: ['Enhancing website security', 'Storing user data to improve the user experience', 'Debugging website code', "Creating website layouts"],
        correctAnswer: 'Storing user data to improve the user experience',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is a "URL"?',
        answers: ['A programming language used for web development', 'A type of website hosting service', 'The address of a web page on the internet', "A web browser's home page"],
        correctAnswer: 'The address of a web page on the internet',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What does "e-commerce" refer to',
        answers: ['The process of optimizing website content', 'Buying and selling products or services online', 'Designing user interfaces for websites', "Managing website databases"],
        correctAnswer: 'Buying and selling products or services online',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is "web accessibility"?',
        answers: ['The practice of ensuring websites are easy to find on search engines', "Designing websites that can be used by people with disabilities", "Developing websites without images", " A type of web hosting service"],
        correctAnswer: 'The practice of ensuring websites are easy to find on search engines',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is "wireframing" in web design?',
        answers: ['The process of designing graphics for a website', "Writing code for a website", 'The process of optimizing website content', "Creating a visual representation of a webpage's layout and elements"],
        correctAnswer: "Creating a visual representation of a webpage's layout and elements",
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is the purpose of "HTTPS" in a web address?',
        answers: ['Indicating that a website is not secure', "Encrypting data transmitted between a user's browser and the website", " Identifying the website's IP address", "Increasing the website's loading speed"],
        correctAnswer: "Encrypting data transmitted between a user's browser and the website",
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What does "DNS" stand for in web technology?',
        answers: ['Data Navigation Service', 'Dynamic Network Security', "Domain Name System", "Digital Naming Service"],
        correctAnswer: 'Domain Name System',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is "A/B testing" commonly used for in web development?',
        answers: ["Testing website performance on various browsers", 'Comparing two versions of a webpage to determine which one performs better', 'Debugging website code', "Creating website content"],
        correctAnswer: 'Comparing two versions of a webpage to determine which one performs better',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: '"HTML" is a programming language used for web development',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: '"CMS" stands for "Content Maintenance System" in web development',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: `"Responsive design" means that a website's layout adapts to different screen sizes`,
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: '"JavaScript" is a widely-used programming language for both front-end and back-end web development',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: '"Web hosting" refers to the process of optimizing website content',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
    ],
  };


  export const multipleQuizAdvance = {
    totalQuestions: 15,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is the primary purpose of "caching" in web development?',
        answers: ["Enhancing website security", "Storing frequently used data to reduce load times", "Debugging source code", "Creating website layouts"],
        correctAnswer: 'Storing frequently used data to reduce load times',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What does "asynchronous programming" refer to in web development?',
        answers: ["Executing tasks independently, without waiting for each other to finish", "A coding style that focuses on synchronous execution", "Creating complex user interfaces", "Managing server-side databases"],
        correctAnswer: 'Executing tasks independently, without waiting for each other to finish',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is the role of a "content delivery network (CDN)" in website performance?',
        answers: ["Storing website backups", "Debugging website code", "Distributing website content across multiple servers to reduce latency", "Designing user interfaces"],
        correctAnswer: 'Distributing website content across multiple servers to reduce latency',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is "minification" in the context of web development?',
        answers: ["The process of optimizing images on a website", "Creating visual layouts for a website", "Managing website databases", "Reducing the size of files, such as JavaScript or CSS, to improve website speed"],
        correctAnswer: 'Reducing the size of files, such as JavaScript or CSS, to improve website speed',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What does "serverless computing" mean in web development?',
        answers: ["Developing websites without servers", "Executing code on servers without the need to manage server infrastructure", "Debugging website code", "Creating website content"],
        correctAnswer: 'Executing code on servers without the need to manage server infrastructure',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is the purpose of "load balancing" in web server architecture?',
        answers: ["Distributing incoming web traffic across multiple servers to ensure optimal performance", "Enhancing website security", "Writing code for a website", "Creating website layouts"],
        correctAnswer: 'Distributing incoming web traffic across multiple servers to ensure optimal performance',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What does "SQL injection" refer to in web security?',
        answers: ["The process of improving a website's search engine ranking", "A type of website hosting service", "Developing front-end components of a website", "A security vulnerability where malicious SQL queries are injected into input fields"],
        correctAnswer: 'A security vulnerability where malicious SQL queries are injected into input fields',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is "version control" in software development?',
        answers: ["Debugging website code", "Developing databases for websites", "The practice of tracking and managing changes to source code", "Designing user interfaces"],
        correctAnswer: 'The practice of tracking and managing changes to source code',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What does "scalability" mean in the context of web applications?',
        answers: ["The ability to handle increasing amounts of web traffic or data without a drop in performance", "Debugging source code", "Enhancing website security", "Creating visual layouts for a website"],
        correctAnswer: 'The ability to handle increasing amounts of web traffic or data without a drop in performance',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is "WebAssembly" used for in web development?',
        answers: ["A web hosting service", "A low-level programming language for high-performance web applications","Debugging website code", "A type of content management system (CMS)"],
        correctAnswer: 'A low-level programming language for high-performance web applications',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: '"Responsive design" refers to designing websites that adapt to different screen sizes',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: '"JavaScript" is a server-side programming language commonly used in web development',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: `"GraphQL" is a query language for APIs that allows clients to request only the data they need`,
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: '"MVC" is an acronym for "Model View Controller," a software design pattern commonly used in web applications',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: '"Single-page applications (SPAs)" load a single HTML page and dynamically update the content as the user interacts with the app',
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
    ],
  };